The wedding isn't over yet
Let's get the certificate first
Documents are complete
Marriage registration is
a serious matter
Do you both confirm this is voluntary
I confirm
It's not too late to back out
Mr Fu
this is the third time you've asked
I'm not backing out
I confirm
In this life
My name finally belongs to me
You two can go take the photos now
Is it too much to
dress like this for the photo
A bride in a wedding dress
taking certificate photos
It's quite rare
Today is quite special
Groom step a little closer
Don't look so serious
It's a marriage certificate
not an ID photo
No need to look like
you're under interrogation
I've never taken one before
Look at the camera
don't frown and smile a bit
Congratulations to you both
Wishing you a happy marriage
In this life
I've truly broken free